Time to partner up, class. I want you to hold hands when you've found your one, okay?
Hey, wanna be with me?
Sure.
Has everybody paired off?
Seems we have an odd man out.
Hey, kids, who wants Miyamura to be their second partner?
No way.
He's gross. And really weird, too.
We'll be conducting an experiment.
But before we do anything, break into groups of five.
And melancholy Miyamura's solo yet again.
Like, I can never get a solid weed on that guy.
Hey! Someone take the leftover!
Yep. About sums it up.
School's pretty tough. In lots of ways.
If they gave out an award for Most Depressing Kid, he'd win every year.
Wait, who would?
Miyamura, duh.
I don't think I know that name.
Seriously? Where have you been? Under a rock?
I heard we're supposed to team up in roster order for this next classics report.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I saw you hide something, though.
Apparently, we're grouped up next project.
Oh, um, that's news to me.
So, uh...
Do you not know my name?
I feel like you should this late in the year, but it's Hori.
I'm sorry.
Huh? I could've sworn she told those girls she didn't know my name, either.
Anyway, people say you're kinda gloomy.
Oh, yeah?
I talked to you so I could see for myself.
And I don't get it.
Cause you seem totally normal to me.
This Hori girl...
Is kinda weird.
I mean...
Yeah
映り変わる季節模様
きっと消えない
今日は言えない
元通りにはもうできない
あの頃に隠した本物はどこ
怒ってくれない
わかってくれない
思ってもただ募ってしまうだけ
懐かしい匂いと
この歌が残る
I found my name!
Looks like I'm gonna be in Class 1 with you, Yugi.
Awesome!
Class 1, Class 1, come on, Class 1.
You guys find your name yet?
Oh, I'm Class 1.
Yes, Class 1 for me too!
This just goes to show how strong the power of love can truly be.
It's fate!
Wait, love?
So because they're in the same class,
they have a faded love?
Is it a romance or are they dating?
Oh yeah!
We'll be together till we graduate!
You guys find your classes yet?
Yep, sure did.
Oh gosh!
I don't think it's worth crying over.
People are whispering.
Then grow up and do something!
Take it easy.
Hit him too hard and you might snap his poor spine.
True!
Oh yeah, Ishikawa.
Remember that song you gave me the other day?
I accidentally deleted it, so...
What?
Come on, dude.
Well, I was trying to free up some storage and then...
Sometimes I wonder...
Extra storage.
I did!
I just have a lot of stuff on it!
Even though I'm in this group,
am I actually one of them?
Or not?
She doesn't need it!
Huh, you're making me want to hear it too.
Okay, I want everybody to split into groups of four for this next project.
Go ahead and team up now.
Miyamura, you're all alone?
Yoshikawa, let me borrow a pen.
You had like a million last time I counted.
You can't even count that high.
And if you're going to be a bully about it, you don't get one.
Well, you suck.
Anybody pick up the packet yet?
Yeah, I have it.
Nice!
Turning the outline into a draft's all hoodie.
Need more paper?
Nah, we should be good.
Miyamura, you've got the chart, cool?
Oh, sure.
Honey!
Toru took my pen and he won't give it back!
Cause I'm still using it, okay?
Knock it off, you two!
Friends.
Can I really call them that?
Are we friends?
Hard to wrap my head around.
I've been looking for you!
Everything cool?
Yeah, no big deal.
Our next class was just switched from math to econ.
I don't think I bought the textbook for that.
When they pull crap like this, it's so unfair.
Listen, man.
I gotta ask you something.
Okay.
So, yeah.
You got any helpful advice?
What?
Wait!
Were you zoning out this whole time?
It's just...
I have a question, too.
Ishikawa.
What, um, what do you think of me?
Asking people that with a straight face is creepy as hell.
As if you getting close with Horty isn't annoying enough.
It's also frustrating how you never say what you mean.
And you're just plain weird.
You're also way too nice to people.
But the real kicker is when you lose the glasses and put your hair up,
you're prettier than most girls I know.
It takes me off.
So I'm a pretty boy?
That's another thing!
You make me say the dumbest shit without even realizing it,
and it drives me freaking crazy!
That's my fault?
If I'm being honest,
I guess I kind of wonder what you think of me too sometimes.
You're one of the few people who still calls me by my last name.
To-
The heck!
Don't say it if you're going to be all bashful afterward, dude!
I'm so sorry!
It just slipped out, but...
Um, truthfully...
Well...
The reason I acted so funny was because that was the first time in high school I called a classmate by their first name.
I swear
You're so weird
Sorry
Don't apologize
I didn't say it was bad
Nothing wrong with being a little awkward
Ain't that right?
Izumi?
I'm okay
I wish I could go back in time ten years
And tell myself that
If you're gonna do a forehead flick
Hold back a little so you don't hit our skulls so hard
I said we'd finish the report over lunch
And you both bail
You better have a good reason
Is affirming our friendship on the roof a good reason?
You're both as creepy as you are stupid
If you're being serious
Hey, if we're stupid then
What does that make Yoshikawa?
And what is that supposed to mean?
Ah, hey
What's up, Ishikawa?
Sleep well?
Huh?
So
I watched that show you were raving about
Izumi
Maybe it's still too soon
But do you have a favorite part?
Let's see
And here I was
Thinking we were on a first name basis now
This guy's a total mystery
Did you hear me?
Hey
Ishikawa?
You done yet, sissy?
Time to go
What?
This early?
Yeah
Yuna's waiting on me
So hurry up
Sota's been getting up way earlier
Now that he's in grade school
Nobody's even here yet
The seat taken?
Oh
Hey, Ayasaki
Remy thought we had a morning assembly today
So she got here early
Yeah, same here
So
That Miyamoto guy is pretty hot, huh?
Uh, is he?
Are you his girlfriend?
Cause he sure act like you are
What?
Nuh-uh
Hmm
You don't say
Well, great
I guess that means Remy can have him then
Huh?
Sorry
Have?
Yeah, he's fair game
So why not?
I mean
I can get as close as I want to Miyamoto
If he's single
Shouldn't make any difference to you, right?
Well, uh
Yeah
Cool
Then Remy calls Dibs
No
Hmm?
There's no Dibs
He's mine
What?
Hold on
How can you claim someone when 30 seconds before you were even dating him?
I'm not giving him to you
Why not?
Because I don't want to
That's why
Remy asked if you're a Miyamoto's girlfriend and you said no
So he doesn't belong to you
I know what I said
And now I'm saying you can't have him
Not ever
Do you hear me?
I'll never let you have him
I hope the cafeteria is open
Well, see ya
I'm so stupid
Miyamoto doesn't belong to anyone
I should be used to these messes by now
But no
I don't care if Sota's in a rush to play
The living room is not his closet
Aw, Sota's M.I.A?
These days he only comes home to change for soccer
Sorry
That's a kid's stamina for ya
You can't do blueberries, right, Hori?
Hmm
Sota's been busier since he started grade school
So Miyamura and I spend a lot more time alone
That fruit tart you brought over the other day was really good
Oh yeah?
Believe it or not, that one was made by yours truly
Look at you, Mr. Talented
Sometimes
We just sort of stop talking
That looked way too real
Come on
It was totally special effects
I bet you're saying that because you're actually scared
And you just don't want to admit it, right?
I know it's fake, because that stuff only happens in movies
Relax, Miyamura
That's the sound of a text, not a demon
Mom's gonna be late again, shocker
I'm so embarrassed
Blackout?
Hey, Hori
Where's your breaker box?
The lights will come back in a second
We're fine
You call this fine?
Wow
That was fast
This house is definitely cursed
The lights came back on, so what's with that face?
Better suck it up, because it's time for disc two
Disc two?
They made more of this awful franchise?
How many are there?
We're gonna watch the first three now
Then we'll do the last two when Sota gets home
What kind of torture is this?
Wow
She was right
You are double-jointed, huh?
Huh?
And your finger
Oh
Your hands are tiny, Yuki
Ooh
Hey, Grabby
Doesn't your heart skip a beat when someone takes your hand?
I don't know
What I do know is you have the cutest little fingers
I bet your hands look little, too, when you compare them to a guy's
Guy's hands aren't near as fun to compare, though
Latch on and you're dead
You hear what she said, Miyamura?
I'm literally risking my life just for the chance to touch Hori's hand
Mine are open and waiting
You can touch away
No thanks
Wow
Your finger's double-jointed
That's so neat, Hori
It makes me unique
Did you break it when you were a kid or something?
No
I was born with it
How does that joint even work, though?
Huh
I'd probably need an x-ray to find out for sure
Wow, you are super pale
Is that callous from writing too much?
Yeah
It's crazy that your hands are bigger than mine
What?
Why is that crazy?
I thought they were smaller for some reason
I like you
Your hands
I really like your hands
They're nice and soft
They are?
Yeah, and my thoughts were so loud they just came out
Maybe it's because I hold my pencil the right way
I don't have calluses like you do
Hey, that was uncalled for
Well, cool
And same
I like yours, too
Yeah?
I like your hands
You said that already
Yeah
I'm back!
Hey, welcome home
Have you washed your hands, Sota?
Not yet
What's with the DVD, bro?
Hori was being a bit of a scatterbrain
And put them in the wrong cases
So I'm swapping them out
Hey, hurry and wash up
It's nearly dinner time
Okay
Oh, Miyamoto
Were you planning on eating with us tonight?
Uh, yeah
I was
Then go show Sota the meaning of the word clean
You got it
Come on
Let's go
Mm-hmm
Then she suddenly got all defensive
She said Miyamoto's hers and Remy can't have him
What?
I was just joking around with her, of course
But Hori got super mad
Well, not the first time you took a joke too far
But still
Hori's scary
She's one girl you don't want to cross
Hi, Miyamoto
What's up?
Nothing much
What the heck happened to your face?
I got punched
And wound up fighting with someone
What?
You got in a fight
But with who?
Ishikawa
You're kidding me
I mean, sure, he's a big dummy dum-dum
But I never thought he'd throw down with a friend
Uh, Hori
Actually, the truth is
I don't want to hear it
Actions speak louder
And this action says all I need to know about what kind of guy he is
Huh?
Morning, Ishikawa
Bro
Holy shit
Toru?
Uh-huh
You called?
Huh?
Mm-hmm
Was it like a fist fight?
Yeah
So, you just punched each other
No, I dodged everything except that first punch
So I guess fist fight might not be the right word
More like I beat him to a bloody pulp
Remind me to never get on your bad side
Why were you fighting?
It's none of your business, Hori
Okay
I guess I'm just having a hard time picturing this whole thing play out
Will you at least tell me who won?
Or is that top secret too?
That's quite a look
Excuse me
Pretty sure I lost
Big time
All I'm saying is I don't see it happening, dude
Hmm
Will you please take this seriously and listen?
You said something's not happening, right?
Hori obviously fell for you
You're as wrong now as you were the first time you said that
It's your imagination
It's not
What if
I knew that it was the truth?
Some kind of test?
If Hori walked in here at this very moment and totally confessed to you
What would your response be?
Would you still brush it off?
It doesn't matter because she just sees me as a friend
Why keep falling back on that lame-ass answer?
Because you keep asking me the same lame-ass question
True
You said it's obvious she likes me
But I'd argue it's more obvious she doesn't
So what are you saying?
Well
Your feelings are involved
And they're having a huge impact on the truth you accept
But you can't assume how Hori feels without asking
Look here!
You startled me so my reflexes took over
Let's see your reflexes handle this
What?
How the hell did we go for talking about feelings to you threatening me?
I guess push came to shove
What's that mean?
It means
Oh shit
Sorry
That hurt
Mercy, mercy
Stop me about him, please
It was self-defense
It's self-defense my ass
Completely uncalled for and irrelevant to Hori is what it was
All this because I startled you?
Not quite
I was also really pissed off
Okay, man
If you're trying to intimidate me, mission accomplished
It's my fault
I pushed Miyamoto past his breaking point
I feel so bad
Then it's settled
So go apologize already
Well
Miyamoto told me he's the reason both of them got so banged up and bruised
What?
Toru says it's his fault
They fight and then they both want the blame
Weirdos
I know
I mean, geez
Why even fight in the first place?
Please don't tell anyone
But we were fighting about Hori
It got intense
What's so funny?
It is kind of cool, though
How guys just duke it out
lol
It sure is
Wantmore
For 16 years
I've seen my dream
The light inside
綺麗な夜に
また明日ねと
手を振る君の姿が
名残惜しくって
長袖のシャツに
見覚えある道
少し寂しそうに見えた
胸が苦しくなるけど
暖かい
気づいた
冬の朝だ
約束するよ
近くにいるから
見えないものほど
大事にするよ
言葉にできないんだけどね
気づいた
落ち着くれて
けども
冷やし